Finding Aid for Band (University of Michigan) records, 1892, 1929-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Band (University of Michigan) records
1892
1929-2012
University of Michigan. Band.
861154 BImu, Bimu F90 2, UBimul F90
Established by students in 1896, the University of Michigan Band had its first salaried director in 1915. The William Revelli era (1935-1971) brought the Band to prominence as the marching, concert, and symphony bands toured and performed extensively, including a tour of Eastern Europe and the Soviet Union by the Symphony band in 1961. Records include scrapbooks of band activities, 1929-1977 (including photographs); bound volumes ("Blue Books"), 1936-present, containing band formations, newsletters, and announcements of band activities, also topical files relating to band tours and concerts. The Marching Band is best documented, although concert band, symphony band, and related ensembles are represented.
8.5 linear feet
76 oversize volumes
38 oversize volumes
1 oversize folders
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
This record group came from multiple sources. Office of the Band (Donor no. 7024 ), George Cavender (Donor no. 6288 ). Posters and photos received from Gregory Munson (Donor no. 9491 ).
The record group is open without restriction.
The Michigan Band was begun in the fall of 1896 as the result of a grassroots student effort. An entirely student-run organization, the band received no support from the university. They first performed at the Law School's annual observance of Washington's Birthday in February 1897, and based on this performance, were granted permission to rehearse in University buildings.
By the fall of 1898, the band was playing at all football games and mass meetings. However, beset with financial problems and internal conflicts, the band took a temporary break in the winter of 1903. The following fall, it was announced that William Hoffman would serve as the band's new conductor and the group began performing at football games again.
Eugene Fischer's direction succeeded William Hoffman. During his years as director, he received little or no remuneration for his services as director of the University band. His advocacy paid off in 1913 when the Board of Regents agreed to fund the band. In the summer of 1915, it was announced that the university had hired Wilfred Wilson to serve as the conductor of the University of Michigan Band. He was the first conductor of the band whose salary was provided by the university. By the time he left Ann Arbor in 1926, the band had grown from 40 members to nearly 100. The band also gained a permanent space in Morris Hall. At this time, the band encompassed two organizations, the Varsity Band and the Concert Band.
In 1926, Wilfred Wilson resigned as conductor of University Bands and was succeeded by Norman Larson, who served as conductor of the Michigan Band for the 1926-27 academic year. In 1927, Nicholas Falcone was appointed as conductor. Despite the protests of many people in Ann Arbor at the time, he admitted African-Americans and women into the band in 1932. However, women were allowed only in the Concert Band. During the Nicholas Falcone years, the Varsity Band's drills were supervised by faculty members of the University ROTC.
In 1935, Falcone resigned due to loss of hearing. The university hired William Revelli to take his place. He required all male wind instrument majors to participate in the Marching Band. (In the fall of 1940, the university took over full management of the School of Music. It had been an adjunct part of the University since 1929.) This requirement greatly increased the number of students in the Marching Band, making the rehearsal space of Morris Hall inadequate. To raise money for the band, Varsity Night, an all-campus talent show sponsored by the University Bands, was begun. By the 1960s, this annual concert had evolved into Band-o-rama which features all six University Bands.
When the United States declared war in 1941, the University of Michigan band was one of the only bands in the country to continue operating. After the war, the Marching Band severed its connections with the ROTC. In 1946, the band moved to a new home, Harris Hall, which during the war had been used as the university USO center. Shortly afterward, in 1948, the Lambda Chapter of Tau Beta Sigma, the National Honorary Band Sorority, was established.
During his time as director, Revelli led the Symphony Band on two tours, including a goodwill tour to Eastern Europe and the Soviet Union in 1961. When Dr. Revelli retired in the summer of 1971, the Michigan Bands consisted of six bands with an enrollment of nearly 500 students. George Cavender succeeded Revelli as Director of University Bands. Through his efforts, funds were raised and a new state-of-the-art facility named Revelli Hall was built to house the Marching Band. Under his direction, women were admitted into the Marching Band in 1972. Cavender was the last person to serve as both Director of Bands and the Director of the Marching Band. He retired as Director of Bands in 1975, and was succeeded by H. Robert Reynolds. After Cavender's retirement from the Marching Band in 1978, Glenn Richter took over for one year as the conductor. He was succeeded by Eric Becher, a native of Ann Arbor, who conducted the Marching Band from 1980-1989. On January 1, 1983, the Marching Band became the first recipient of the Louis Sudler National Intercollegiate Marching Band Trophy.
In 1989, Eric Becher was succeeded by Band Alumnus, Jerry Luckhardt, who in turn was followed by Gary Lewis as Director of the Marching Band in 1990. Lewis left the Marching Band after the 1994 season. In 1995, Band Alumnus Jeff Grogan, served as the interim director and then as assistant director under Kevin Sedatole in 1996. Dr. Sedatole was appointed the Donald R. Shepherd Assistant Professor of Conducting and the Director of the Michigan Marching Band from 1996-1999. Sedatole left after three years and was succeeded by James Tapia, who served as director from 1999-2001. In 2001, many changes took place. Michael Haithcock was hired as the new Director of Bands, replacing H. Robert Reynolds, who retired in 2001 after 26 years. Dr. Tapia left the Marching Band at the same time. Jamie L. Nix, a University of Michigan and School of Music alumnus was hired in 2001 to become the 13th Director of the Marching Band. Nix left in 2006 and was replaced by Scott Boerma in 2007.
Directors of University Bands
1906-1914 Eugene "Ike" Fisher
1915-1926 Captain Wilfred Wilson
1927-1934 Nicolas Falcone
1935-1971 William D. Revelli
1972-1975 George R. Cavende
1975-2001 H. Robert Reynolds
2001-present Michael Haithcock
Directors of the Michigan Marching Band
1906-1914 Eugene "Ike" Fisher
1915-1926 Captain Wilfred Wilson
1927-1934 Nicolas Falcone
1935-1971 William D. Revelli
1971-1979 George R. Cavender
1979-1980 Glenn Richter
1980-1989 Eric A. Becher
1989-1990 Jerry Luckhardt
1990-1995 Gary J. Lewis
1995-1996 Jeff Grogan
1996-1999 Kevin L. Sedatole
1999-2001 James R. Tapia
2001-2006 Jamie L. Nix
2007- Scott Boerma
______________
Sources Consulted
Online history of the Michigan Marching Band, http://mmb.music.umich.edu/history/
A Portrait of a Tradition: One Hundred Years of the Michigan Marching Band (Ann Arbor, MI: University of Michigan Marching Band, 1998)
The University of Michigan Band records are divided into six series: Tours and Concerts, Yearbooks, Photographs and Posters, Audio-Visual Material, Band Books ("Blue Books"), and Scrapbooks. The majority of the records consist of bound volumes of band formations, announcements, and publications, and oversized scrapbooks of band activities. Additional material includes topical files documenting tours and performances. The bulk of the documentation pertains to the Marching Band.
Subjects:
Cavender, George.; College publications.; Music--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Musicians--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Revelli, William D. (William Donald), 1902-1994.; University of Michigan. Band.; Scrapbooks.; University of Michigan--Football.Football.; University of Michigan--Bands.Bands.; University of Michigan. School of Music.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Bands.; University of Michigan. Band.; University of Michigan--Bands.Bands.; Cavender, George.; September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001--Songs and music.
Subjects - Sound Recordings:
Band music.; Football--Songs and music.; Students' songs--United States.; University of Michigan--Songs and music.Songs and music.; Hurrah for the yellow and blue.; Spirit of Michigan.; Halftime classics.; Fire up...it's Saturday.; It's all about blue.
Contributors:
University of Michigan. Marching Band.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Videotapes.; Scrapbooks.; Sound recordings.
- Tours and Concerts, 1926-1965
  The Tours and Concerts series (6 linear ft., 1926-1965) contains papers primarily regarding travel arrangements, concert planning, and news releases for band tours and performances. Includes information relating to football game trips, Varsity Nights, Carnegie Hall concerts, and other special events. The series is divided into Marching Band and University Bands (including Concert and Symphony bands). Information on the 1961 international tour to Eastern Europe and the Soviet Union is included under University Bands. Posters and articles about the tour are housed in an outsize folder.
  - Marching, 1931-1964
    - Princeton Game Trip, October 31, 1931 (Box 1)
    - Ohio Game Trip, October 15, 1932
    - Northwestern Game Trip, November 25, 1933 (Box 1)
    - Minnesota Trip, November 3, 1934 (Box 1)
    - Illinois Game Trip, November 9, 1935 (Box 1)
    - Northwestern Game Trip, October 9, 1937 (Box 1)
    - Pennsylvania Game Trip, November 7, 1936 (Box 1)
    - ROTC Band Formations, 1937/38-1938/39 (Box 1)
    - Yale Game Trip, October 22, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Ohio Game Trip, November 19, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Chicago Game Trip, October 21, 1939 (Box 1)
    - Pennsylvania Game Trip, November 18, 1939 (Box 1)
    - Minnesota Game Trip, November 9, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Harvard Game Trip, October 12, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Columbia Game Trip, November 15, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Notre Dame Game Trip, November 14, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Northwestern Game Trip, October 18, 1941 (Box 1)
    - Northwestern Game Trip, October 5, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Minnesota Game Trip, November 2, 1946 (Box 1)
    - Ohio State Game Trip, November 13, 1945 (Box 1)
    - Northwestern Game Trip, October 18, 1947 (Box 1)
    - Purdue Game Trip, October 9, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Ohio State Game Trip, November 22, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Minnesota Game Trip, October 23, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Rose Bowl Trip, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Band Trips, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Northwestern Game Trip, October 15, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Illinois Game Trip, October 29, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Army Game Trip, October 14, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Minnesota Game Trip, October 28, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Ohio State Game Trip, November 25, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Cornell Game Trip, November 10, 1951; 8 folders (Box 2)
    - Rose Bowl Trip, January 1, 1951; 7 folders (Box 2)
    - Northwestern Game Trip, October 18, 1952 (Box 2)
    - Ohio State Game Trip, November 22, 1952 (Box 2)
    - Minnesota Trip, October 24, 1953 (Box 2)
    - Michigan State Trip, November 14, 1953 (Box 2)
    - Michigan Bands, 1953-1954 (Box 2)
    - Michigan Marching, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
    - Northwestern Game Trip, October 16, 1954 (Box 2)
    - Ohio State Game Trip, November 20, 1954 (Box 2)
    - Marching, 1955-1956 (Box 2)
    - Marching Band Clinic, 1955 (Volume 1)
    - Minnesota Game Trip, October 22, 1955 (Volume 2)
    - Michigan-Illinois Game Trip, November 5, 1955 (Volume 3)
    - Marching, 1956-1957 (Volume 4)
    - Iowa Game Trip, November 3, 1956 (Volume 5)
    - Marching Band Clinic, 1956 (Volume 6)
    - Marching, 1957-1958 (Volume 7)
    - Minnesota Trip, 1957 (Volume 8)
    - Iowa Game Trip, November 2, 1957 (Volume 9)
    - Marching, 1958-1959 (Volume 10)
    - Michigan State Trip, October 4, 1958 (Volume 11)
    - Northwestern Trip, October 18, 1958 (Volume 12)
    - Marching, 1959-1960 (Volume 13)
    - Indiana Trip, November 14, 1959 (Volume 14)
    - Marching, 1960-1961 (Volume 15)
    - Michigan State Trip, October 1, 1960 (Volume 16)
    - Wisconsin Trip, October 28-29, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Marching, 1961-1962 (Box 3)
    - Minnesota Trip, October 27-29, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Marching, 1962-1963 (Box 3)
    - Michigan State Trip, October 13, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Purdue Trip, October 20, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Marching, 1963-1964 (Box 3)
    - Minnesota Trip, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Marching Band European Tour, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Marching, 1964-1965 (Box 3)
    - Michigan State Trip, October 10, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Ohio State Trip, November 20-21, 1964 (Box 3)
  - University Bands, 1926-1965
    - Correspondence, 1926-1945; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Papers Concerning Varsity Night Performances, 1946-1955; 5 folders (Box 3)
    - Papers Concerning the City Concerts, 1934-1950; 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Papers Concerning the Spring Tours, 1948-1949; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Papers Concerning the Philadelphia Concert, 1952 (Box 3)
    - Michigan Bands, 1953-1954 (Box 4)
    - University Bands News Releases, 1953-1954 (Box 4)
    - Papers Concerning the Symphony Band Mid-Semester Tour, 1954 (Box 4)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, 1954 (Box 4)
    - Michigan Bands Tour Arrangements, 1954-1955 (Box 4)
    - University Bands News Releases, 1954-1955 (Box 4)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, 1955; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Carnegie Hall ticket Arrangements, April 8, 1955 (Box 4)
    - Carnegie Hall concert, April 8, 1955 (Box 4)
    - Symphony Band Between Semester Tour, 1955 (Box 4)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, 1956 (Box 4)
    - Varsity Night Concert, October 13, 1956 (Box 4)
    - Orchestra Hall Ticket Orders, December 14, 1956 (Box 4)
    - Symphony Band December Tour, 1956 (Box 4)
    - Symphony, 1955-1956 (Box 4)
    - Michigan Bands Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box 4)
    - University Bands News Releases, 1955-1956 (Box 4)
    - Michigan Bands-Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 4)
    - Symphony, 1956-1957 (Box 4)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, 1957; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Varsity Night, October 11, 1957 (Box 4)
    - University Bands News Releases, 1956-1957 (Box 4)
    - Varsity Night, October 31, 1958 (Box 4)
    - University Bands News Releases, 1957-1958 (Box 4)
    - Symphony, 1957-1958 (Box 4)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, 1958; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Symphony, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
    - University Bands News Releases, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
    - Philadelphia Orchestra, 1958-1959 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, March 30-April 5, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Varsity Night, October 16, 1959 (Box 5)
    - Carnegie Hall Concert, March 28, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Carnegie Hall Concert Ticket Orders, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, 1960; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Dave Brubeck Quartet, September 23, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Symphony, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
    - University Band News Releases, 1959-1960 (Box 5)
    - Stan Kenton Show, 1960 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Requisitions, 1960-1961 (Box 5)
    - Symphony, 1960-1961 (Box 5)
    - University Bands News Releases, 1960-1961 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Four Freshmen, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Russian Tour, 1961 (Box 5)
      (See also Box 8 for foreign newspaper coverage, and tour posters in outsize folder-UBimul F90)
    - Symphony Band Russian Tour News Releases, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Carnegie Hall Concert, June 1961 (Box 5)
    - Carnegie Hall Concert Ticket Requests, 1961 (Box 5)
    - Carnegie Hall Ticket Orders filled, 1961 (Box 5)
    - University Bands News Releases, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Future Concerts, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Requisitions, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
    - Symphony, 1961-1962 (Box 5)
    - MENC Trip, March 16-18, 1962 (Box 6)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Victor Borge, October 5, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Between Semester Tour, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Symphony, 1962-1963 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Symphony, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
    - University Bands News Releases, 1963-1964 (Box 5)
    - Al Hirt Sextet, October 4, 1963 (Box 5)
    - Future Concerts, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Spring Tour, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Victor Borge, October 16, 1964 (Box 5)
    - Symphony Band Weekend Tour, 1965 (Box 5)
    - Survey on Band Awards (Box 5)
- Yearbooks, 1981-1995
  The series Yearbooks (15 volumes) contains published annual yearbooks for the Marching Band covering the period 1981 to 1995. See also the Audio-Visual Materials series for Marching Band video yearbooks.
  - 1981-1995, 15 volumes (Box 7)
- Photographs and Posters, 1892; 1949-1980
  The series Photographs and Posters (1892, 1949-1980) is comprised of outsized photographs and posters. Photographs include the Symphony Band, 1958-1963, various "Band Day" events, a 1970s football formation, and a 1980 formation spelling out Revelli. Also included is an 1892 group photo identified as "University of Michigan Band." Posters announcing concerts during the period 1958 to 1963 are included along with several large format posters from the Soviet Union and Eastern Europe promoting the band's 1961 tour. Foreign newspapers on the 1961 tour are also included.
  - Photographs
    - 1892 (Box 8)
    - circa 1940 (Box 8)
    - 1951 (Box 8)
    - Band Day (located in outsize folder-UBimul F90), 1949 (Folder UBimul-F90)
    - Band Day Chart, 1951 (Box 8)
    - Band Day (located in outsize folder-UBimu F90), 1952 (Folder UBimul-F90)
    - Symphony, 1958/1959 (Box 8)
    - Symphony, 1960 (Box 8)
    - 1960 (Box 8)
    - Symphony, 1962-1963 (Box 8)
    - Football Formation (color), circa 1975 (Box 8)
    - Revelli Formation, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Posters
    - 1958-1963 (Box 8)
    - Russia and Eastern Europe Tour, 1961 (Folder UBimul F90)
  - Foreign Newspapers from Russia Tour, 1961
- Audio-Visual Material
  Audio-Visual Material (1985-2001), includes VHS videotapes, CD recordings, and an audio cassette featuring the Marching Band. Videotapes include "Take the Field" volume I (1985), II (1989), and III (2001) highlighting field performances, and segments from trips and concerts. "A Michigan Tribute" contains footage from the September 22, 2001 performance where tribute was paid to the victims of September 11. Other videotapes include Marching Band Video Yearbooks from 1991 to 1999. Audio recordings include commercial compact diss recordings of Marching Band standards and performance highlights from 1977 to 2001. One audiocassette recording, "Fire Up... It's Saturday" is also available in a CD version.
  - Audio Recordings
    - Audio Cassette, 1 audiocassettes
      - "Fire Up... It's Saturday: Highlights of The Michigan Marching Band, Eric A, Becher, Conductor,", circa 1980s (Box 9)
    - Compact Discs
      - "Halftime Classics: The University of Michigan Marching Band 1977-1978 George R. Cavender, Conductor," 1978, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 9)
      - "Fire Up... It's Saturday: Highlights of The Michigan Marching Band, Eric A, Becher, Conductor,", circa 1980s; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 9)
      - "A Saturday Tradition,", 1993; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 9)
      - "Hurrah for the Yellow and Blue: Michigan Marching Band, Kevin L. Seatole, Director,", 1998; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 9)
      - "Michigan Championship Celebration, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 9)
      - "The Spirit of Michigan: Michigan Marching Band, Men's Glee Club, Women's Glee Club,", 1998; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 9)
      - "It's All About Blue: Marching Band 1999-2000,", 1 optical disks CDs (Box 9)
  - Videotapes (VHS)
    - George Cavender Interview with Jeff Wohl, March 1998; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 9)
    - Michigan Marching Band Video Yearbook, 5 videotapes VHS (TM)
      - 1990 (Box 9)
        (copyright 1991)
      - 1991 (Box 9)
      - 1995 (Box 9)
        (copyright 1997)
      - 1996 (Box 9)
        (copyright 1998)
      - 1999 (Box 9)
    - "A Michigan Tribute" (Victims of September 11, 2001), 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 9)
    - "Take the Field" Volume I, 1985; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 9)
    - "Take the Field" Volume II, 1989; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 9)
    - "Take the Field Volume III Saturday Fantastique,", 2001; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 9)
- Band Books - "Blue Books", 1927-2012
  The Band Books, also called "Blue Books," (76 volumes, 1936- 2012) are a nearly complete run of bound volumes created by the Marching Band containing band formations, rosters, announcements, section news, and event programs. The years 1936-1945 are bound together in one volume. More recent years consist of multiple volumes. There are no volumes for the years 1947-1948, 1979, 1981-1982, or 1984.
  - 1936-1945 (Volume 17)
  - 1946, 1 folders (Volume 18)
  - 1949-1951 (Volume 19)
  - 1952 (Volume 20)
  - 1953 (Volume 21)
  - 1954 (Volume 22)
  - 1955 (Volume 23)
  - 1956 (Volume 24)
  - 1957 (Volume 25)
  - 1958 (Volume 26)
  - 1959 (Volume 27)
  - 1960 (Volume 28)
  - 1961 (Volume 29)
  - 1962 (Volume 30)
  - 1963 (Volume 31)
  - 1964 (Volume 32)
  - 1965 (Volume 33)
  - 1966 (Volume 34)
  - 1967 (Volume 35)
  - 1968 (Volume 36)
  - 1969 (Volume 37)
  - 1970 (Volume 38)
  - 1971 (Volume 39)
  - 1972 (Volume 40)
  - 1973 (Volume 41)
  - 1974 (Volume 42)
  - 1975, 2 volumes (Volume 43)
  - 1976 (Volume 44)
  - 1977 (Volume 45)
  - 1978 (Volume 46)
  - 1980 (Volume 47)
  - 1983 (Volume 48)
  - 1985 (Volume 49)
  - 1986 (Volume 50)
  - 1987 (Volume 51)
  - 1988 (Volume 52)
  - 1989 (Volume 53)
  - 1990 (Volume 54)
  - 1991 (Volume 55)
  - 1992 (Volume 56)
  - 1993, 2 volumes (Volume 57)
  - 1994, 2 volumes (Volume 58)
  - 1995, 2 volumes (Volume 59)
  - 1996, 2 volumes (Volume 60)
  - 1997, 2 volumes (Volume 61)
  - 1998, 2 volumes (Volume 62)
  - 1999, 2 volumes (Volume 63)
  - 2000, 2 volumes (Volume 64)
  - 2001, 2 volumes (Volume 65)
  - 2002, 2 volumes (Volume 66)
  - 2003, 2 volumes (Volume 67)
  - 2004, 2 volumes (Volume 68)
  - 2005, 2 volumes (Volume 69)
  - 2006, 2 volumes (Volume 70)
  - 2007, 2 volumes (Volume 71)
  - 2008-2009, 2 volumes (Volume 72)
  - 2010-2011, 2 volumes (Volume 73)
  - 2011-2012, 2 volumes (Volume 74)
- Scrapbooks
  The Scrapbooks series (38 oversize volumes, 1929-1977) richly documents band activities and social events between 1929 and 1977 through newspaper clippings, programs, and photographs. All bands (marching, symphony, concert, ensembles) are included in the scrapbooks.
  - [Vol. 1], 1929-1945 (Volume 1)
  - [Vol. 2], 1935-1952 (Volume 2)
  - [Vol. 3], 1946-1949 (Volume 3)
  - [Vol. 4], 1948 (Volume 4)
  - [Vol. 5], 1949-1950 (Volume 5)
  - [Vol. 6], 1950 (Volume 6)
  - [Vol. 7], 1951 (Volume 7)
  - [Vol. 8], 1951 Rose Bowl (Volume 8)
  - [Vol. 9], 1952-1953 (Volume 9)
  - [Vol. 10], 1953-1954 (Volume 10)
  - [Vol. 11], 1954-1955 (Volume 11)
  - [Vol. 12], 1955-1956 (Volume 12)
  - [Vol. 13], 1956-1957 (Volume 13)
  - [Vol. 14], 1957-1958 (Volume 14)
  - [Vol. 15], 1958-1959 (Volume 15)
  - [Vol. 16], 1959-1960 (Volume 16)
  - [Vol. 17], 1960-1961 (Volume 17)
  - [Vol. 18] Soviet Union Tour, 1961 (Volume 18)
  - [Vol. 19], 1961-1962 (Volume 19)
  - [Vol. 20], 1962-1963 (Volume 20)
  - [Vol. 21-22], 1964-1965 (Volume 21)
  - [Vol. 21-22], 1964-1965 (Volume 22)
    (continued)
  - [Vol. 23], 1964-1969 (Volume 23)
  - [Vol. 24] Rose Bowl, 1965 (Volume 24)
  - [Vol. 25-26], 1965-1966 (Volume 25)
  - [Vol. 25-26], 1965-1966 (Volume 26)
  - [Vol. 27], 1966 (Volume 27)
  - [Vol. 28], 1966-1967 (Volume 28)
  - [Vol. 29], 1967-1968 (Volume 29)
  - [Vol. 30], 1968-1969 (Volume 30)
  - [Vol. 31-32], 1969-1970 (Volume 31)
  - [Vol. 31-32], 1969-1970 (Volume 32)
  - [Vol. 33], 1971-1972 (Volume 33)
  - [Vol. 34], 1972-1973 (Volume 34)
  - [Vol. 35], 1973-1974 (Volume 35)
  - [Vol. 36], 1974-1975 (Volume 36)